export const mockState = {
  JavaScript: {
    title: 'JavaScript',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'JavaScript Question 1?',
        answer: 'JavaScript Answer 1'
      },
      {
        question: 'JavaScript Question 2?',
        answer: 'JavaScript Answer 2'
      }
    ]
  },
  React: {
    title: 'React',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'React Question 1?',
        answer: 'React Answer 1'
      },
      {
        question: 'React Question 2?',
        answer: 'React Answer 2'
      }
    ]
  }
}

export const mockNewDeckState = {
  JavaScript: {
    title: 'JavaScript',
    questions: []
    }
  }

export const mockNewQuestionState = {
  JavaScript: {
    title: 'JavaScript',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'JavaScript Question 1?',
        answer: 'JavaScript Answer 1'
      }
    ]
  },
  React: {
    title: 'React',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'React Question 1?',
        answer: 'React Answer 1'
      },
      {
        question: 'React Question 2?',
        answer: 'React Answer 2'
      }
    ]
  }
}

export const mockQuestion = {
  question: 'JavaScript Question 2?',
  answer: 'JavaScript Answer 2'
}

export const mockDeck = {
    title: 'JavaScript',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Question 1?',
        answer: 'Answer 1'
      },
      {
        question: 'Question 2?',
        answer: 'Answer 2'
      }
    ]
  }
